the subscription price is going to drop
va a bajar el precio de la suscripción
that means there's no excuse
eso quiere decir que ya no hay excusa
to play crash on a new channel I
para jugar al chocar en un canal nuevo
put the link on twitter have you
he puesto el link en el twitter os
subscribed to the new channel that the
habéis suscrito al canal nuevo que el
new channel in the dick puts more salsa and
canal nuevo en la [__] pone más salsa y
filter by channels and you search for more salsa salsa
filtrar por canales y buscas más salsa
songs appear yes but you hit
te aparecen canciones de salsa sí pero
filter and put channels is she
le das a filtrar y pones canales está
very upset or Isabella because of the
muy molesta o isabella por la bajada de
price drop why why because she's
precio por qué por qué porque está
upset contract if more
molesta contraer si se suscriben más
people subscribe it's preferable to have three thousand
gente es preferible tener tres mil
subscribers of one euro than to have 100
suscriptores de un euro que tener 100
subscribers of four euros who will no longer
suscriptores de cuatro euros que ya no
earn well man of course let's see
va a cobrar bien hombre claro a ver
because there will surely be many people who are
porque seguramente habrá mucha gente que
paying the 5 dollars a month
estén pagando los 5 dólares mensuales
seeing as paying less to pay me
viendo pagar menos para pagarme
delivered also on the other hand there will be
entregado también por otra parte habrá
more people who subscribe god knows there are
más gente que se suscriban a saber dios
two ways the subscription is a
que haber dos manera la suscripción una
voluntary thing you can't force
cosa voluntaria tú no le puedes obligar
people to subscribe or who can't
a la gente a que se suscriba o que no
be very heavy like me but
puede ser muy pesado como yo pero yo
even the one who can't subscribe
hasta el que no se pueda suscribir
because he can't adapt five dollars
porque no se puede adaptar cinco dólares
a month or he's going to give you two dollars in bits
al mes o te va a dar dos dólares en bits
maybe but that person if those  two
a lo mejor pero esa persona si esos dos
dollars you can invest to subscribe
dólares lo puede invertir suscribirse
because you are going to subscribe sometimes each
pues se va a suscribir a veces que cada
one is going to continue spending what they
uno se va a seguir gastando lo que
want to spend there are people who spend
quiera gastarse hay gente que se gasta
a lot of money
mucho dinero
even monthly between donations and
incluso al mes entre donaciones y
subscription and then they can
suscripción y entonces puede se pueden
spend 100 euros 200 euros between what you
gastar 100 euros 200 euros entre que se
can afford you not to do it
lo pueda permitir usted no hacerlo una
once you can't get angry about it I mean the
vez no te puedes enfada por eso o sea la
people who spend what they want to
gente que se gaste lo que quiera
spend equality grateful you have to be
gastarse igualdad agradecido tienes que
here let's see if Gonzalez
estar acá vamos a ver si gonzález la
has it x people who spend here
tiene x personas que se gastan aquí
have them per month he is going to continue having them they are
tienen al mes los va a seguir teniendo
going to continue spending the same what do you
se van a seguir gastando lo mismo que
prefer 3,000 subscribers who pay one
prefiere 3.000 suscriptores que pagan un
euro or 200 who pay 4 pay those
euro o 200 que paguen 4 paga esas
tricks to the accounts he doesn't give much
chicanas a las cuentas no le da mucha
thought to it I was very distressed I think he does
vuelta estaba muy afligida yo creo que
n't give it or I think he doesn't give it
no la da o yo creo que no la da vuelta
obviously if it is cheaper than I don't
evidentemente si está más barato que no
know what the price will be just a
sé cuál será el precio sólo de una cosa
super logical thing to lower the price
súper lógica que bajen el precio date
realize the best 5 Europe Europe is
cuenta al mejor 5 europa la europa está
fine 5 euros a subscription in Europe
bien 5 euro una suscripción en europa
is fine but for Latin America it
está bien pero para latinoamérica no
is not good 5 dollars  5 dollars for
está bien 5 dólares 5 dólares para
Latin America the subscription with dollars
latinoamérica la suscripción co dólares
in Latin America a lot is
en latinoamérica mucho es que es de
logical, no, he even said that he was going to have to
lógica no hasta dijo que se iba a tener
move to a place in Spain please
que mudar a un lugar de españa por favor
how drastic but why don't you turn it around
que drástica pero porque no la da vuelta
I know how many things they will buy you but it is
en sé cuántas cosas te comprarán pero es
a price for a subscription in
un precio para una suscripción en
Latin America today in which they spend 25
latinoamérica hoy en el que se gastan 25
dollars on a subscription in
dólares en una suscripción en
Latin America it will continue to be tied
latinoamérica se lo va a seguir atando
but in any case, by putting the
pero de todas maneras que al poner los
prices cheaper it is not that you are going to
precios más baratos no es que vayas a
earn less it is that you are going to earn
ganar menos es que vayas a ganar
and they put it at half the pressures that
y lo ponen a la mitad de presiones que
streamer is going to earn half it is going to
streamer vaya a ganar la mitad va a
earn more because more people are going to subscribe
ganar más porque se va a suscribir más
daughter another imagine by making it cheaper
gente hija otro imagínate al abaratarlo
the number of people who are going to subscribe to the
la de gente que se va a suscribir a los
big ones to Lauro employs Libya all those
grandes a lauro emplea libia todos esos
years and they are putting a price
años y se lo están poniendo un precio
that can be five dollars in Chile three
que puede cinco dólares en chile tres
thousand 562 which is nothing I don't know I don't know the
mil 562 lo cual es nada no sé no sé la
economy I don't know how much it equates to
economía no sé a cuánto equipara
understanding that there are salaries there that
entendido que por allí hay sueldos que
are 200 euros or 300 euros less he said
son de 200 euros o 300 euros menos dijo
that he was going to have to sell his body in
que iba a tener que vender su cuerpo en
what sense
qué sentido
Karime, you're sending me this message because of
karime me mandas este mensaje por lo de
Gonza Vela. She said that referring to the fact that
gonza vela eso dijo refiriéndose a que
the IFAB, the small stream sima
al ifab a la sima de stream en pequeñas
could affect them, they're not going to have more guarantees, she
les puede afectar no va a tener más lo
said it jokingly, and I say it as if I
dijo en broma avales y lo digo como
were exaggerating, I'm not going to have to
exagerando no voy a tener que ponerme a
do a live and live and she said that those
hacer un live and live and dijo que los
who will pay more, which triples, if
que pagarán más lo que se triplica si
you know what a good idea it was
ustedes sabéis la buena idea que fue
when I put the members
cuando yo puse en los miembros
at various prices, obviously whoever
a varios precios evidentemente el que
can and wants to, will sign up for the
pueda y quiere pues se va a apuntar al
five euro price, but there are a lot of people,
de cinco euros pero hay muchísima gente
of the three thousand members, which is more
de los tres mil miembros que somos más
than a thousand, at the cheap price of a euro,
de mil al precio de lata que un euro
but those thousand, if it weren't there, it would be
pero esos mil si no estuviera se
pressed at approximately 440 dollars, the
presionaría 440 dólares aprox sueldo
minimum wage in Chile. I'm telling you, you
mínimo en chile eso te digo ya no le
can no longer charge without charging a
puedes cobrar sin cobro de una
subscription, I mean, you can't ask
suscripción o sea no le puedes pedir a
someone from Latin America to spend the
alguien de latinoamérica que se gaste lo
same on a subscription as on the payment
mismo en una suscripción que en la letra
for their car, since it's not, I'm saying it,
de su coche ya que no es lo digo
guys, I do my best super well, the
chavales yo lo doy todo súper bien la
truth is, it seems more than logical to me, it
verdad me parece más que lógico me
seems more than that in Chile today, with five
parece más que el hoy en chile con cinco
current dollars you can have a
dólares actuales puedes verte un
complete hot dog, a portion of
completo hot dog una porción de papas
fries  and if you get a juice of life like that, it's about
fritas y si alcanza un jugo de vida así
eating, I think that these
de comer se trata yo creo que las
tantrums are what put
pataletas éstas así echan para atrás a
people off when it comes to subscribing, everyone
la gente a la hora de suscribirse a cada
does what you want, God, you can
uno hace lo que quieras dios puedes
complain because people stop from the map of
quejarte porque la gente para de mapa de
less than one who does what they believe and
menos de uno que haga lo que crea y
corresponds who wants to invest in their
corresponda que quiera invertir en su
streamer no
streamer no
and they are equally grateful
y ya está igualmente agradecido
equally grateful minimum wage in
igualmente agradecido salario mínimo en
Colombia 250 dollars or 200 euros who is
colombia 250 dólares o 200 euros quién
going to pay some subscriptions well the
va a pagar unas suscripciones bueno los
rich the rich in Mexico it happens a lot from what I
ricos los ricos en méxico pasa mucho por
understand in Mexico it happens a
lo que tengo entendido en méxico pasa
lot that very poor people or are very
mucho de que la gente muy pobre o es muy
rich that we are going to get angry let's
rica que vamos a estar cogerse un enfado
see where I can see the anger
a ver dónde lo puedo ver el enfado me
can you tell me
podéis decir
the small and medium ones above all
los pequeños y medianos sobre todo sabio
totally wise the first and I always
totalmente el primero y siempre
mean guys you are going to continue
me refiero chicos vosotros vais a seguir
having prime I mean the prime they are
teniendo prime me refiero a los prime
not going to remove the valuable prime it is not
no van a quitar los prime valiosas no es
that it is not about removing
que no se trata de que vayan a quitar
the sprites no no it is that this what they
los sprites no no es ese el este lo que
are doing is that they are going to energy
están haciendo es que los van a energía
me explain what they are going to do is that the
me explico lo que van a hacer es que los
sprites in the middle  receive well I don't
sprites en medio recibir bueno que yo no
receive 5 dollars for nothing, I mean I
recibo 5 dólares por nada o sea yo
always receive half, can someone
recibo siempre la mitad alguien puede
say how many ubs does the
decir cuántos ubs tiene bolsa vela de
two dollar vela bag have the suvs well for that
dos dólares las suvs pues ya por ese
prime I'm going to receive a dollar that has
prime voy a recibir un dólar que tiene
300 subscribers 732 it's not that much it's not
300 suscriptores 732 tampoco es tanto no
a damage it's a confinement it's 1.5 dollars
es un daño es un confín es 1.5 dólares
already but if you multiply if you multiply
ya pero si multiplicas si multiplicas
by 700 subs it's a lot of money 700 money
por 700 subs es mucho dinero 700 dinero
so let's see, I have, I'm
entonces a ver yo yo tengo yo tengo la
lucky I mean I don't earn it
suerte me refiero de que yo no lo gano
badly I mean I don't earn just enough
mal me refiero o sea no lo gano lo justo
to get through the month it's not that much or much
para pasar el mes no es eso ni muchísimo
less January but imagine the people who
menos enero pero imaginar la gente que
but obviously I'm not going to be affected
pero obviamente no voy a ver afectada
by this I've already said that I don't know if I'm going to have to
por esto ya he dicho que no sé si me voy
spend 24/7 on tweets to be
a tener que pasar 24/7 en tweets para
able to one night but well, likewise
poder una noche pero bueno de igual
people who really earn just enough to
gente que realmente gana lo justo para
get through the month and this is their job and this
pasar el mes y este es su trabajo y esto
is an income that means a lot to get through the
es un ingreso que le supone la [__]
month or
para poder llegar a fin de mes o lo que
whatever maybe it's not even their
sea a lo mejor ni siquiera es su trabajo
main job I sincerely think that this that
principal yo sinceramente opinó que esto
this is going to hurt
que esto va a perjudicar más a los
streamers more  that help them especially the
streamers que ayudarlos sobre todo a los
small and medium sized but really
pequeños ya los medianos pero realmente
Tucumn yes but if maybe you have many
tucumán sí pero si tal vez tienes muchos
more subs but really I mean the people
más subs pero realmente osea la gente
who don't want to subscribe
que nos y que no se quiere suscribir con
for five euros or who can't
por cinco euros o que no se puede
subscribe for five euros I don't think they'll
suscribir por cinco euros no creo que lo
do it because they put it at four euros
hagan porque lo pongan a cuatro euros
for example as is the case in Spain in
por ejemplo como es el caso de españa en
Latin America I don't know but if the attack the
latam no lo sé pero si el ataque los
salaries are so tight they were very
salarios son tan ajustados eran muy
low they are wrong 25 euros or spending
bajitos se equivocan 25 euros o gastarse
2 avast is 5 dollars or 15 in pesos in
2 avast es de 5 dólares o 15 en pesos en
pesos as it is worth but spending 65 dollars
pesos como vale pero gasta 65 dólares
to spend two dollars it still
para gastarse dos dólares sigue
supposes money that they need
suponiendo un dinero que les hace falta
for something else so really the
para otra cosa entonces realmente la
gang was based I don't think so well it's that I don't know I don't
peña se basó no creo pues es que no sé
know I think that I repeat I hope I hope I'm
no sé yo creo que repito ojalá ojalá
wrong I hope I'm wrong I hope
ojalá me equivoque ojalá me equivoque
it's real
ojalá real
and this is a brutal improvement for twitch
y esto sea una mejora brutal para twitch
damn what more do I want them to make improvements
[__] que más quiero que haga mejoras
for the extremes and for the biohuertos
para los extremos y para los biohuertos
or rather what more do I want but but I
o sea que más quiero yo pero pero yo
believe in Mexico the increase to  cost
creo en mexico la suba a costar dos
exactly two dollars that's going to come to me
dólares exactos a ese a mi me me va a
imagine if someone
llegar imagínate si alguien
someone some Mexican who sees me doesn't
alguien que algún mexicano que me vea no
write to this channel it's going to cost me
está escribe a este canal le va a costar
two dollars it's going to come to me one dollar
dos dólares a mí me va a llegar un dólar
yes but three times as many people are going to subscribe
sí pero se va a suscribir triple de
seriousness plus taxes plus the
gente seriedad más impuestos más el
PayPal change my
cambio de paypal se me va a quedar la
super is going to be at 0 50 or something like that so I'm going to
súper en 0 50 o cosas así entonces voy a
earn 1 with 1 with 7 now more or less
ganar 1 con 1 con 7 ahora más o menos
that I earn for his to the 05 that I'm going to earn
que ganó por su a los 05 que voy a ganar
from subs and people subscribe to me from
por subs y la gente se me suscribe desde
the so Mexico or whatever I
la tan méxico o lo que sea yo
sincerely don't see it or rather I think that
sinceramente él no lo veo o sea creo que
or rather for you obviously it
o sea que para vosotros obviamente me
seems good to me but that the decrease
parece que está bien pero que la bajada
is compensated with the increase in SUVs
se compensada con el aumento de suvs
but that's not the case, I mean the the ones
pero es que eso no es así o sea los los
that I repeat do you really think that I'm going to
es que repito de verdad creéis que voy a
suddenly have from going from having 700
tener de repente de pasar a tener 700
subs I'm going to have 1,400 and 2,000
subs voy a pasar a tener mil 400 y 2000
because that's what it is what I would more or
porque es es lo que es lo que más o
less need to compensate for the
menos necesitaría para compensar la
loss on the one hand
pérdida por un lado
I noticed it man  I noticed it's incredible do
yo lo noté tío yo lo noté increíble
you remember when I put the price can
os acordáis cuando puse el precio lata
remember people plin plin plin plin
acordáis la gente plin plin plin plin
subscribing to death but before they
suscribiéndose a muerte pero antes
could subscribe to a channel now they
podían suscribirse a un canal ahora
can stopped that it's mathematics come on
pueden parados que es matemática vamos
the mathematics does not fail equally in that it does
las matemáticas no fallan igualmente en
not reach as much public to that
que no llega a tanto público a ese
public that reaches be 50 viewers
público que llegue sean 50 espectadores
60 to 100 I do not know how many will have light and
60 a 100 no se los que tendrá de luz y
of those 50 viewers that they usually have
de esos 50 espectadores que suelen tener
now you do not have in each live 50-60
ahora no tienes en cada directo 50-60
viewers but in reality they are a thousand
espectadores pero en realidad son mil
subscribers a thousand followers sorry for
suscriptores mil seguidores perdón por
those thousand followers if maybe you have
esos mil seguidores si a lo mejor tiene
20 30 40 subscribers surely there will
20 30 40 suscriptores seguramente va a
be many more even on that small
haber mucha más incluso a esa pequeña
scale it will not notice it obviously on
escala no lo va a notar evidentemente a
that small scale there will be more people
esa pequeña escala va a haber más gente
who subscribe but as it
que se suscriba pero a medida que vaya
grows then it will be interesting because in the
creciendo pues va a interesar es que al
end we will see in the end a person
final vamos a ver al final una persona
who sometimes absurd what we are
que a veces absurdo lo que estamos
talking about because if you are telling me
hablando porque si tú me estás diciendo
that a strident viewers and 50 south worth that you
que un estridente viewers y 50 sur vale
reach 670 dollars a month 8
que llegas a los 670 dólares al mes 8
for the minimum to be able to collect okay
para el mínimo para poder cobrar vale
that  you will notice instead of charging 70
que vas a notar en vez de cobrar 70
dollars you will charge 40 it is not going to
dólares vas a cobrar 40 no te va a
solve your life equally understand
solucionar la vida igualmente entiende
now
ahora
meditate that it begins to have a little
medita que empieza a tener un poquito
more currently the minimum wage in
más actualmente el salario mínimo en
Mexico is 123 pesos a day and 5
méxico es de 123 pesos al día y 5
dollars are 99 pesos for many it will be
dólares son 99 pesos para muchos será
impacted and sad face
impactado y cara triste
understand a stream in which he charges
comprende un stream en el que cobre
60-70 dollars a month because if he is going to charge
60-70 dólares al mes pues si va a cobrar
less than let's see we are already talking about that
menores que a ver ya ya estamos hablando
for example an expert right now
de que por ejemplo un perito ahorita
has his 100 200 spectators that
tiene sus 100 200 espectadores que no
we are not talking about going from 100 dollars
estamos hablando de pasar de 100 dólares
to 50 dollars for me to charge blind
al 50 dólares para mí para cobra ciegos
charges 50 in the minimums the same I do the
cobra 50 en los mínimos el mismo hago
same in the end it does not give you enough to
una lo mismo al final no te da para
live but for a streamer like maybe
vivir pero para un streamer como a lo
the expert who starts a
mejor ya el perito que empieza un
little already grows at the moment that you
poquito ya crece en el momento que tú
start to grow and begins to have if it
empiezas a crecer y empieza a tener si
is 200 spectators 300 spectators to maybe
es 200 espectadores 300 espectadores a
go from having 100
pasar a lo mejor de tener 100
subscribers to having 300 400 cameras that I
suscriptores a tener 300 400 cámaras que
can tell you myself the change  I
te lo puedo decir yo mismo el cambio lo
noticed brutal damage the change I noticed it
noté brutal daño el cambio lo noté
brutal when I realized that on
brutal cuando me di cuenta que en
YouTube you could put the members at one
youtube se podía poner los miembros a un
euro and two euros and I learn you
euro y a dos euros y aprendo tú
wanted brutal do you remember that day
quisieras brutal nos acordáis ese día
that they were made in one day I don't remember
que se hicieron en un día no me acuerdo
if 400 or 500 members in one day of course
si 400 o 500 miembros en un día claro
everyone is going to notice it a
que lo va a notar todo el mundo a una
person who is very very very small who
persona que sea muy muy muy pequeña que
is starting out who has 50 viewers it is
esté empezando que tenga 50 espectadores
obviously going to be harmed in the
evidentemente le va a perjudicar en el
sense that instead of 100 dollars they
sentido de que en vez de 100 dólares la
charge 50 to 40 or 60 obviously but
cobra 50 a 40 ó 60 evidentemente pero no
we are not talking about those amounts
estamos hablando de esas cantidades
we are talking about when it starts to
estamos hablando de cuando empieza a
grow a little bit just like the per
crecer un poquito quito así como el per
and it is a little bit a person who is
y está un poquito una persona que esté
generating 100 dollars a month generates 60
generando 100 dólares al mes genera 60
people will think less about buying
la gente se lo pensará menos en comprar
an SUV and it will be beneficial for stream
una suv y será beneficioso para stream
it is since more people will buy unasur the
es ya que más gente comprará unasur los
big channels not the
canales grandes no a los canales
small channels like me or the perito also
pequeños como yo o el perito también lo
notice it the only thing that is going to be most
nota lo único que se van a ver más
affected are the channels that are
afectados son los canales que están
starting okay yes but it already takes the
empezando vale sí pero es que ya lleva
same to generate  100 dollars a month
da lo mismo generar 100 dólares al mes
to generate 60 is over is not going to get you out of
que generar 60 se acabó te va a sacar
trouble, that I don't know if I'm
ningún apuro eso no sé si me estoy
explaining myself grams which is better and besides it's
explicando gramos que es mejor y aparte
not that it's better or
no es que se trate de que sea mejor o
worse for the streamer it's that it's logical it's that it
peor para el streamer es que es lógico
's logical it's a tin person ca
es que es lógico es una persona de lata
n't spend well can't
no puede gastarse bueno no puede por lo
generally spend five euros I imagine
general gastarse cinco euros me imagino
that Netflix these platforms in
que netflix estas plataformas en
Latin America will not be worth five dollars
latinoamérica no valdrán cinco dólares
not the same as here I don't imagine I don't
no igual que aquí no me imagino
know but I imagine that if you
desconozco pero me imagino que si tú
generate 60 dollars it accumulates for the following month
generas 60 dólares acumula para el mes
also
siguiente
YouTube has a minimum to collect which
youtube tiene un mínimo para cobra que
is 100 dollars and if it had
son 100 dólares y si tuvo un me genera
40 dollars it generates me that accumulates until it
40 dólares que acumular lo hasta que
accumulates 100 dollars to collect no no no you
acumule 100 dólares para cobrar no no no
lose it I don't know what that money twist
lo pierdes no sé que ese dinero twist
accumulates no then it's not bits if I'm not
acumula no entonces no es bits si no me
mistaken they are going to continue exactly the same like they are
equivoco van a seguir exactamente igual
not going to touch and they are going to continue
en plan no se van a tocar y van a seguir
costing the same it will be about the subject
costando lo mismo va a ser sobre el tema
of their being, I mean it will be only only the
de su ser o sea va a ser sólo sólo el
subject of SUVs so I don't think
tema de suvs así que no creo que se
the  price drop with the
comience la bajada de precios con el
moment of going up and I don't believe it either, I
momento de subir y tampoco lo creo yo
just think there will be people who maybe do
sólo creo habrá gente que a lo mejor sí
take it and well, look, since I
que coge y pues mira pues como me gusta
really like this content creator, well,
muchísimo este creador de contenido pues
I think that in reality all the people
yo creo que en realidad toda la gente lo
record it, in reality, people like to
graba en realidad a la gente le gusta
collaborate with their stream but just for
colaborar con su stream pero ya por
fun because they have the pleasure of collaborating, I do
gusto porque tiene el gusto de colaborar
n't know if I'm explaining myself like when you
no sé si me explico en plan cuando tú
're comfortable with someone who
estás a gusto con a alguien que te
entertains you every day you spend a lot of
entretiene todos los días pasan mucho
time with that streamer, I think
rato con ese streamer yo creo que la
people have the pleasure of becoming
gente tiene el gusto de hacerse
subscribers and they feel like they're
suscriptor y se siente como que está
contributing to the cause, they understand, and those who do
aportando en la causa entiende y el que
n't do it because they can't, and many
no lo hace porque no puede y muchas
times maybe they managed to make it
veces a lo mejor lo logró ponerlo más
cheaper, well, maybe I subscribe to a
barato pues a lo mejor me suscribo en un
cold workshop and that's it, I do
taller frío y ya está
n't think many people will do that
no creo que muchísima gente haga eso
because honestly it didn't work out, for example,
porque sinceramente no salió por ejemplo
I know that I'm not going to do it and I'm
yo yo sé que no lo voy a hacer y estoy
subscribed to a lot of channels, okay, I'm
suscrita a un montón de canales vale soy
subscribed to, as I'm not exaggerating, like 15
suscrita como no exagero como a 15
channels,
canales o sea
but I'm not going to do it obviously, I'm not
pero no lo voy a hacer obviamente yo no
going to subscribe to a free workshop because it's
me voy a suscribir un taller free porque
like I'm subscribed to many
es como yo estoy suscrita a muchos
channels, you know, maybe the  I do it
canales sabéis a lo mejor el uno lo hago
in one but no I don't think so what you're trying to say
en uno pero no no lo creo está queriendo
with this today kids don't
decir con esto hoy de chavales no lo
do it legally in Argentina in the
hagáis en legales en argentina en la
five dollar Twitch subscription
suscripción de cinco dólares de twitch
would be equivalent to 12 or 13
equivaldría a 12 o 13 membresías nivel
my weapon level memberships since YouTube Pacific
mi arma ya que youtube pacific a las
purchases 4 dollars in bed make a good
compras 4 dólares en la cama hacen buena
difference I see the logic but look it's
diferencia yo le veo lógica pero mira es
that way for me this of complaining about
que tos manera a mí esto de quejarse por
this look at this puts people off
esto mira esto echa para atrás la gente
and let's see people yes yes there are people
y vamos a ver la gente sí sí hay gente
who put it at half price they say ok yes
que se lo pone a mitad de precio dice ok
let's look how I was paying five
si vamos mira como estaba pagando cinco
euros but I do have it at half
euros pero yo sí lo tengo a la mitad de
price I'm going to take it at half price
precio voy a [__] de mitad de precio
but then if that person wants to give these two or
pero luego si esa persona estos dos o
three euros in vite they're
tres euros que los quiere dar en vite lo
going to get stuck in a row it
van a trabas seguidas igualmente tiene
seems to me I'll give you my money because I
me parece yo te doy mi dinero porque de
really like to support you in addition to your
verdad me gusta apoyarte además de tu
great charisma and way of thinking that you are
gran carisma y forma de pensar que eres
great Javi thank you very much has given well thank you very much
grande javi muchas gracias ha dado pues
thank you very much
agradece muchísimo agradeció muchísimo
you know equally I did it for a month no and if a
sabéis igualmente hice un mes no y si un
month instead of being subscribed 3,000
mes en vez de estar suscritas 3.000
people there are  months that maybe it's
personas hay meses que a lo mejor está
2000 2000
2000 2000
today in which they can man an
hoy en los que se puedan hombre una
obligation is not the one that can I
obligación no es el que pueda yo de
truly appreciate it from the bottom of my heart
verdad que lo agradezco de mucho corazón
and the beat or things obviously
y los beat o las cosas evidentemente
but don't see me what to do if you don't do it hey well that's it well it will
pero no me veas qué hacer si no lo
be because you ca
hacéis oye pues ya está pues será porque
n't or because maybe
no se puede o porque a lo mejor esté
your belly is less having so many
menos tu vientre teniendo tanto a la
people whatever it is that are complaining about making
gente lo que sea que se está quejando de
it cheaper god look or I
que lo pongan más barato dios mirada o
mean in fact I'm going to show you
sea de hecho os voy a enseñar
a thread that I bet -13 this one is very
un hilo que apuesto -13 ésta está muy
well explained I'm going to show it for a while
bien explicado lo voy a enseñar un rato
to read it all and the truth is that it
para leerlo todo y la verdad es que
looks pretty good for the consumer
pinta bastante bien para el consumidor
beware but bad for the creator and above
beware pero mal para el creador y sobre
all it looks great for amazon super like
todo pinta genial para amazon super like
that and opening it giving my opinion it's going to be
a eso y abrirlo dando mi opinión va a
long and as I think this is the
ser largo y como creo que esto es la
prelude to eliminating them prime totally that this this is this is
antesala de eliminarlos prime totalmente
this campaign to be
esa esto es esto es esta campaña para
able to give away their obviously really
poder regalar su evidentemente de verdad
super mega something else is born to finish off
super mega otra cosa nace para acabar
the pranes because obviously amazon
con los pranes porque obviamente amazon
doesn't profit from continuing to pay prime it doesn't
no les renta seguir pagando prime no le
profit it doesn't profit to continue paying prime
renta no le renta a seguir pagando prime
and taking into account that the majority  part
y teniendo en cuenta que la mayor parte
of the communities are supported by
de las comunidades se sustentan
buying at least Spanish speakers
comprando por lo menos hispanohablantes
okay that's it the biggest the biggest abel
vale eso la mayor la la mayor abel no
we can't confirm the intention of having
podemos confirmar la intención de tenga
more or not with the issue of whether he wants to
más o no con el tema de si quiere
delete it to order it for him and it would
suprimirlo para encargárselo para ya mí
seem absurd to me that both or he
me parecería absurdo que ambas o se
wants to get rid of it and that he can't
quiera quitar encima y que no pueda
maintain that the tweets are not profitable for
mantener que no le salga rentable los
him because I don't have a contract with
tweets yo porque no tengo contrato con
twin and I'm a partner but since I'm
twin y soy partner pero como estoy
still testing because I don't have navero I'm
probando todavía por no tengo navero os
speaking to you from what I speak with my
hablo por lo que hablo con mis
colleagues and
compañeros y demás
others apparently tweets pay a tremendous amount compared to youtube with ads okay for example these 100 thousand visits that he has with shabelle here in the viewers the ads that appear in the live and so on
que aparezcan en el directo y demás por
apparently in ads I know people who
lo visto en anuncios conozco a gente que
have 8,000 or 10,000 subs and apparently they
tiene 8.000 o 10.000 subs y por lo visto
charge much more for the ads they
cobran mucho más por los anuncios que
carry now that must be because they
portan ya eso se tiene que deber a que
pay a large percentage the problem with
pagan un gran porcentaje el problema de
youtube is that youtube apart from all the
youtube es que youtube aparte de todo lo
yellow liquor and all the [ __ ] is
de licor amarillo toda la [__] está
only from the ads youtube
solo de los anuncios sea youtube se
keeps 55  percent of what you
queda con un 55 por ciento de lo que tú
generate to us on youtube we charge
generas a nosotros en youtube cobramos
45 of what they generate so surely
el 45 de lo que generan pues seguramente
tweets keeps a smaller percentage
tweets se quede con un porcentaje más
and gives more to the creators which
pequeño y le dé más a los creadores que
is how it should be from an individual point of view
es como debe ser desde punto de vista
because they are the ones creating
porque son los que están creando
content more than anything even if you provide
contenido más que nada aunque tú pongas
the platform you pay your commission to
la plataforma tú le pagas tu comisión a
the platform but the creator is
la plataforma pero el creador es
then I think that if tweets
entonces yo creo que si tweets no
could not maintain a profitable output
pudiera mantener una salida rentable
something would be to increase the percentage of what they
algo sería subir el porcentaje de lo que
keep for the ads there is no more
se quedan por los anuncios no hay más
money there than in prime time surely
dinero ahí que en los prime seguro que
part of the
parte de las comunidades
Spanish-speaking communities are supported based on
hispanohablantes se sustentan a base de
prime time
prime time
this tracker what do you think
este tracker qué opinas
based on price the tweets tracker
a base de price lo de tweets tracker
this I think is less reliable than
este yo creo que es menos fiable que el
sociable and twitter that you can see
sociable y twitter a que tú puedes ver
you can see the number of members but
tú puedes ver el número de miembros pero
you don't know who is subscribed at what
tú no sabe quién está suscrito a qué
level how many are given away the
nivel cuántas son regaladas nos los
views like that could be seen one hundred
vistos así se podían ver al cien por
percent once the same but I don't know if it is
cien una vez lo mismo pero no sé si es
very reliable
muy fiable
you can't see what someone generates
tú no puedes ver lo que genera alguien
from ads let's see but I know
por anuncios a ver pero yo conozco
some that have five thousand eight thousand and
alguno que tienen cinco mil ocho mil y
a handful of subscribers and me  They
un puñado sin de suscriptores y me
say they earn a lot more for
cuentan que ganan muchísimo más por
Lans the summary of what is going to happen in
lanús el resumen de qué va a pasar en
many countries almost all of them going to be reduced to special
muchos países casi todos a especial a
subscriptions well
suscripciones va a verse reducido bueno
what they tell me to those who are not going to be
lo que me dicen a los que no se va a
adjusted to their local currency as you can see
ajustar a su moneda local como veis
they themselves only cite five
ellos mismos sólo sólo citan cinco
exceptions or in other words it is going to continue costing
excepciones o sea va a seguir costando
exactly the same at that time the
exactamente lo mismo en ese entonces los
dv6 streams are barely going to be
streams dv6 apenas se van a ver
affected by this this girl
perjudicados por esto esta chica de
really doesn't know anything if it is going to
verdad no se entera de nada si va a
continue costing the same in the
seguir costando lo mismo en estados
United States and as you say my weapon does not
unidos hubiese y como tú dice mi arma no
mean that it is not going to affect
quiere decir que no les va a afectar a
those who commit crimes there it depends
los de crímenes que vivan allí depende
on where your audience is I can be
de donde sea tu audiencia yo puedo ser
from Almera from there from Rocket also but
de almería de allí de rocket además pero
that my audience is from Yue it is understood
que mi audiencia sea de yue se entiende
then it does not affect me it does not affect you where
entonces no me afecta no te afecta donde
your life affects you from wherever your audio is
tu vida te afecta de donde sea tu audio
my soul which is like that can be from Mexico
mi alma que es así puede ser de méxico
but that your Spanish audience because you
pero que tu audiencia española porque tú
upload content in Spanish that has a
subes contenido en español que tiene
large Spanish audience maybe it is
mucha audiencia española a lo mejor es
Mexican maybe the Mexican has an
mexicano a lo mejor el mexicano tiene un
English channel and your audience is from
canal en inglés y tu audiencia es de
New York I was in the cpm I don't know
nueva york estuve el cpm no sabe no se
a real girl moved in the on
trasladó una chica de verdad en la en
that page  for a company it does not take into
esa página para empresa no tiene en
account the contracts because many the
cuenta los contratos porque muchos el
first channel of course apart from that that is
primer canal claro aparte de eso eso es
important it is also good that it can
importante también es bueno que pueda
be an idea but apart from Maria that what
ser una idea pero es que aparte maria
the buckle is saying is
eso lo que está diciendo la hebilla es
important also there is a lot of the first
importante también hay mucho del primer
that have different contracts there are
que tienen contratos diferentes hay
some that charge half of each subscription
algunos que de cada suscripción cobran
there is another that charges 70 in
la mitad hay otro que cobran un 70 en
Canada this I think is Swiss yes Switzerland
canadá esto creo que es suizo si suiza
Israel and Japan for the first chickens
israel y japón para los primeros pollos
are the ones that are going to be applied the most well it is
son los que más se va a aplicar bueno
equivalent to 243 for that of Mexico 1 or
equivale a 243 para el de méxico 1 o sea
for example in Turkey it will be 119
por ejemplo en turquía va a ser 119
dollars and in Mexico 2.43 dollars
dólares y en méjico 2,43 dólares
the first thing that all this implies is the
lo primero que implica todo esto es la
improvement in the price for the consumer
mejora en el precio para el consumidor
for Bioware obviously and above all it will be
por bioware obviamente y sobre todo será
justice with countries with bad economies
justicia con países con mala economía ya
since it made no sense for an SUV
que no tenía ningún sentido que una suv
for that the same in a sem burgo as in
para eso lo mismo en un sem burgo que en
Venezuela value third so
venezuela valor tercero
that side that is
así que ese lado por eso
very good in fact it was time that
muy bien de hecho ya era hora de que
they put prices according to each country and
pusieran precios acordes a cada país y
with its own currency
con su propia moneda
perfectly written and perhaps it
perfectamente escribirse y quizás no
could not now have it more within your reach
podía ahora lo tenga más a su alcance
like that  that's good for the community so
así que bueno para la comunidad así que
good for the community too I repeat I
bueno para la comunidad también repito
think that someone who couldn't
creo que alguien que no se podía
subscribe for 5 dollars I do
suscribir a 5 dólares no sé si se va a
n't know if they're going to assume they're going to subscribe for two dollars absurd logically the help in Thessaloniki I think that someone who couldn't subscribe for five dollars won't be able to for two it's like if I take and say this loot is worth four euros in this loot I
vale cuatro euros en este botín yo antes
couldn't afford it before because it cost
no me lo podía permitir porque costaba
200 dollars and now you take an offer
200 dólares y ahora se coge una oferta
that's worth 10 dollars or nothing it's that if I can't
que valen 10 dólares o nada es que si no
afford it I'm sorry I can't
me lo puede permitir lo siento tampoco
afford it either ten dollars of
me lo puedo permitir diez dólares de
doctors talking you know please and the
doctores hablando sabe la por favor y el
-3 is obviously you can afford
-3 es evidentemente te puedes permitir
things when the price reductions
las cosas cuando las rebajas de precio
if for me if I were very very
si a mí si yo estuviera muy justa muy
fair in plan to make ends meet
justa en plan para llegar a fin de mes
if I could barely pay everything that I have to
si apenas pudiese pagar todo lo que
pay I really really
tengo que pagar creo de verdad realmente
think I wouldn't subscribe or I mean at
creo que no me suscribiría o sea como
most I would subscribe to a channel to a
mucho que suscribiría a un canal a un
channel that I love being but I wouldn't
canal que me encanta ser pero no estaría
subscribe to 15 channels like in my case is
suscrita 15 canales como es mi caso es
that I subscribe to 15 channels as
que estoy suscrita a 15 canales como
well for  you but look at Gonza Vela,
bien para ti pero mira gonza vela
cheap that they took out barefoot like that wouldn't be like that
barato que sacaron descalzo así no sería
then I really don't know if someone who ca
entonces realmente no sé si alguien que
n't afford five lares is going to be
no se puede permitir cinco lares se va a
able to afford two or three dollars on the
poder permitir dos o tres dólares al
other side this way we have the
otro lado de esta manera tenemos los
creators and for that we this will
creadores y para ello nosotros esto
probably be a change but I hope
probablemente sea un cambio pero espero
before explaining why I have to
antes explicar el por qué tengo que
clarify because I think this benefits
aclarar porque creo que esto beneficia
Amazon more it's here in more benefits
más a amazon está aquí en más beneficios
it's Amazon Twitch Villa mind both are
es amazonia twitch villa mente ambas son
going to charge what you poor or a
va a cobrar lo que tú pobres o
percentage of what you charge
porcentaje de lo que tú cobre
depending on the streamer it's worth but amassed it's
dependiendo del streamer vale pero amasó
also going to benefit because more
también le va a beneficiar porque más
people are going to be members and well let's
gente se va a ser miembro y bueno vamos
think about this girl's salsa the
pensando en el salsero de esta chica la
truth is that they bore me
verdad que me aburren